hiddengemsbooks.com 2019-06-18

# Privacy Policy - Hidden Gems Books: ARC Reviews and Book Deals

**Last updated: (May 24, 2018)**

Hidden Gems (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates http://www.hiddengemsbooks.com (the “Site”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.

### **Information Collection and Storage**

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your email address. We never sell, lease, or loan your personal information to third parties. By providing this information to us, you acknowledge your consent to have your data processed by the Site.

Information may be stored on our secure servers or on those of affiliate entities (including Mailchimp) and will be retained indefinitely. You can [contact us](mailto:contact@hiddengemsbooks.com) at any time to request deletion of your data.

### **Information Processing**

Information collected by the Site may be stored and processed in the United States, Europe, or any other country with affiliated entities or subsidiaries. If you are located in the US, EU, or other region with laws governing data collection, we will not transfer any information (including your personal information) to any country that does not have equal or greater data protection laws as your home jurisdiction.

### **Information Use**

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information. Should you wish to receive fewer of these messages, or none at all, simply use the links provided in each message to change your preferences or unsubscribe from the contact list.

We use your Personal Information only for the purposes of providing access to our Advance Reader Copy (“ARC”) Program, displaying advertisements, and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

### **Log Data and Analytics**

Like many site operators, we may collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site.

This data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

We may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this data.

### **Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads. Google’s use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to the Site and/or other sites on the Internet.

You may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). (Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting[ www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).)

### **Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

In the event of a system security breach, we will inform you and the relevant authorities in accordance with applicable law.

### **Access, Correction, and Deletion of Your Data**

At any time, you can request to know which data we have about you, can make any corrections to that data, or request that we delete all of your data by [contacting us](mailto:contact@hiddengemsbooks.com).

### **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of June 30, 2017 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason, with or without notice. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy, so please check it periodically.

### **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](mailto:contact@hiddengemsbooks.com).
